

MOCHAMAD GALIH RAMDHANI

www.mcgalihramdhani.com
mcgalihramdhan@gmail.com



ABOUT ME

I graduated from UIN Syarif Hidayatullah Jakarta majoring in Physics with a focus on Instrumentation Physics. Experience in analyzing experimental data has leverage my skills in identifying problems and troubleshooting capabilities. I have an understanding of hardware (computer and robot hardware) and software (Arduino, Python) based on my experience in disassembling and designing hardware and also creating program algorithms.

BIODATA

 Age
 : 24

 Sex
 : Male

 Height
 : 171 cm

 Weight
 : 60 kg

Address : Jl. Kyai Maja RT 03/RW 03, Kel. Panunggangan,

Kec. Pinang, Kota Tangerang 15143

Nationality : Indonesia

EDUCATION

Universitas Islam Negeri Syarif Hidayatullah Jakarta

May 2017 – January 2023

Bachelor of Science in Physics, GPA: 3.52/4.0

COURSES

RevoU (online course)

RevoU Mini Course Digital Marketing

RevoU (online course)

RevoU Fundamental Course Software Engineering

RevoU (online course)

RevoU Mini Course Data Analytics

SKILLS

Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PPT)
Object oriented programming (Arduino, Python)
Web design (HTML, CSS, Javascript)
Graphic design (Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere Pro)

EXPERIENCES

Laboratory Assistant

UIN Syarif Hidayatullah Jakarta | 02/2021 - 12/2021

- Checking and calibrating the tools before doing experiments
- Leading and teaching the student how to operate and achieve the result as cited in the practitioner module for several courses
- Correcting and assessing student experimental reports

Graphic Designer

HIMAFI UIN Syarif Hidayatullah Jakarta | 08/2018 - 01/2019

- Create an instagram posts
- · Create a nametag design
- · Create a banner design

PROJECTS

Automatic moving Charity Box

Github link: github.com/mcgalih/Charity-Box-Car

- Designed a storage box device that can move automatically and following the track line
- Control the device movement by placing a hand in front or behind of the device

Card Security System Charity Box

Github link: github.com/mcgalih/Charity-Box-Card

- Designed a storage box device that can only be opened by certain card(s)
- Can register a new card(s) as a key

Nomor liazah Nasional SK BAN-PT APT [Nilai]

452012023000168

: No. 25/SK/BAN-PT/Akred/PT/II/2018 [A] SK BAN-PT PRODI [Nilai] : No. 6929/SK/BAN-PT/Ak-PPJ/S/XI/2020 [B]



KEMENTERIAN AGAMA REPUBLIK INDONESIA UNIVERSITAS ISLAM NEGERI SYARIF HIDAYATULLAH JAKARTA



Memberikan Kepada:

Mochamad Galih Ramdhani

Lahir pada tanggal 12 Januari 1999 di Tangerang

IJAZAH SARJANA SAINS (S.Si.)

: Sains dan Teknologi **FAKULTAS**

Fisika PROGRAM STUDI

NOMOR INDUK MAHASISWA : 11170970000002

NOMOR INDUK KEPENDUDUKAN / PASPOR : 3671111201990001

TANGGAL LULUS : 27 Januari 2023

Dengan segala hak dan kewajiban yang berhubungan dengan gelar akademik ini.





Jakarta, 24 Februari 2023

Dekan

Ir. Nashrul Haklem, S.Sl., M.T., Ph.D NIP.19710608 200501 1 0054



Universitas Islam Negeri SYARIF HIDAYATULLAH JAKARTA

TRANSKRIP AKADEMIK

Nomor Ijazah Nasional : 452012023300168

SK BAN-PT APT [N lai] : No. 25/SK/BAN-PT/Akred/PT/II/2018 [A]

MOCHAMAD GALIH RAMDHANI

: Tangerang, 12 Januari 1999

: 11170970000002

: 31

Judul Skripsi

Rancang Bangun Kotak Amal Berjalan Otomatis Dengan Fungsi Deteksi Gelap-Terang Lantai.

Nomor Transkrip : B.F.9.ER 073692.2023

: Sains dan Teknologi Fakultas

Program Studi

Tempat/Tgl.Lahir

: Fisika

IPK

NIM

Jenjang

Jumlah Kredit

3,52

: 161 SKS

Tanggal Lulus	:	27 Januari 2023	Predikat Kelulusan	2	Sangat Memuaskan		

Kode	Matakuliah	SKS	Nilai	Kode	Matakuliah	SKS	Nilai	Kode Matakuliah	SKS Nilai	Kode	Matakuliah	SKS Nila
HS 6003	BAHASA ARAB	3	A	FIE 4078	PEMROGRAMAN SISTEM INSTRUMENTASI	3	Α					
HS 6001	BAHASA INDONESIA	3	A	ris 5082	PENDAHULJAN FISIKA INTI	4	Α					
HS 6002	BAHASA INGGRIS	3	В	POL 2002	PENDIDIKAN KEWARGANEGARAAN	2	5					
10 2019	BICLOGI JMUN	2	В	FIS 5072	PENGOLAHAN SINYAL DIGITAL	2	4					
TS 6069	DASAR-DASAR TELEKOMUNIKASI	3	A	FIS 4010	PRAKTEK BENGKEL	2	4					
IS 4017	EKSPERIMEN FISIKA 1	2	В	ABI 6027	PRAKTEK KERLA LAPANGAN	3	Д					
IS 6017	EKSPERIMEN FISIKA 2	2	В	FIS 4031	PRAKTIKUM ELEKTRONIKA	1	В					
IS 5142	ELEKTORNIKA LANJUT	2	В	FIS 6139	PRAKTIKUM ELEKTRONIKA LANJUT	1	A	Marie Control of the				
18 4033	ELEKTRONIKA	3	В	FIS 3013	PRAKTIKUM FISIKA DASAR 1	1	Α	The state of the s				
IS 3003	FISIKA DASAR I	3	Α	FI3 4014	PRAKTIKUM FISIKA DASAR 2	1	٨			ľ		
18 4003	FISIKA DASAR 2	3	в	FIS 4092	PRAKTIKUM FISIKA KOMPUTASI	1	В					
IS 4015	FISIKA KOMPUTAS	3	В	SAR 2002	PRAKTIKUM IBADAH	1	A					
IS 6004	FISIKA KUANTUM	4	Α	KIM 3047	PRAKTIKUM KIMIA DASAK	1	C					
13 5005	FISIKA MATEMATIKA 2	4	В	FIS 6029	PRAKT KUM MICROPROSESOR	1	Α	A STATE OF THE PERSON NAMED IN COLUMN TWO IS NOT THE OWNER.				
IS 4005	FISIKA MATEMATIKA I	4	В	FIS 5081	PRAKT KUM PENGOLAHAN SINYAL DIGITAL	1	A	A STATE OF THE STA				
IS 5007	FISIKA MODERN	3	А	SAR 2001	PRAKTIK JM QIROAH	1	В	100000000000000000000000000000000000000				
15 6018	FISIKA STATISTIK	1	В	FIS 3089	PRAKTIKUM SISTEM DIGI <mark>TA</mark> L	1	Α					
1S 502C	FISIKA ZAT PADAT	4	Α	TIS 3088	PRAKTIKUM SISTEM KENDALI	1	A					
FT 2237	GELOMBANG	3	В	FIS 5074	FOBOTIK	3	Α					
15 4002	ILMU PEDAGOGIK	2	В	JIN 4265	SEMINAR SKRIPSI	1	Α					
IS 5071	INSTRUMENTASI FISIKA MEDIS	3	В	F185070	SISTEM DIGITAL	2	A					
A G 2002	ISLAM DAN ILMU PENGETAHUAN	3	Α	FIS 6074	SISTEM KENDAL	2	Α	Market Market				
MAT 3018	KA_KU_US 1	.9.	A	FIS 8065	SISTEM SENSOR	3	В			West .		
1AT 4018	KALKULUS 2	3	В	STA3023	STATISTIKA	3	В	and the second s			D	
ABI 2019	KEW RAUSA IAAN	2	В	SAG 6001	MAJSHIGHTS	4	А			Jakar.a, 24 Feb	uari 2023	
CIM 3015	EIMIA DASAR	2	B	FIE 6072	TEORI RANGKAIAN	5	А		1	Dekan	0	
ABI 5013	KULIAH KERJA NYATA (KKN)	3	Α	FIS 5014	THERMODINAMIKA	5	Α		1/4	COX. X	•	
IS 3083	MEDAN ELEKTROMAGNET 1	4	ь	ABI 9014	SKRIPSI	6	A		1/2/			
TIS 7085	MEDAN ELKTROMAGNET 2	3	В						(*	· UI	ern, S.Si., M.T., Ph.D	
IS 5021	MEKANIKA	4	В							NIP 19:10608		
IS 6021	MEKANIKA KI ASIKA	Ž.	A						1/18	4KAR 19 10608	0000110051	
MA" 4036	METODE NUMERIK	2	Α							BY IK INDO		
ABI 3021	METODOLOGI PENELITIAN FISIKA	3	A							III THE LITTLE OF		
FIS 506?	MICROPROSESOR	3	С					EN STATE OF THE ST				
POL 2001	PANCASILA	2	Λ	1						and the same of th		